<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arnie Cheong on The ArnieBarnie</title>
    <link>https://aforlorncat1.github.io/authors/hugo-authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Arnie Cheong on The ArnieBarnie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aforlorncat1.github.io/authors/hugo-authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Get better at Hacka(Data)-thons</title>
      <link>https://aforlorncat1.github.io/blog/get-better-at-hackadata-thons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aforlorncat1.github.io/blog/get-better-at-hackadata-thons/</guid>
      <description>Over the past week I participated in Hong Leong Bank&amp;rsquo;s(HLB) annual Can You Hack It 2020 Datathon, and managed a top 10 finish after pitching to a (digital) panel of C-suite and M.D. level judges. The experience was certainly eye-opening and very hard-earned, with my nearly throwing in the towel at multiple points throughout the event.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to share a little on the event itself, the problem and my motivation towards the solution, and the lessons I&amp;rsquo;d be bringing into my next hackathon, which I hope would be useful to you, dear reader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopee Code League Challenge No. 1</title>
      <link>https://aforlorncat1.github.io/blog/shopee-code-league-challenge-no.-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 18:55:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aforlorncat1.github.io/blog/shopee-code-league-challenge-no.-1/</guid>
      <description>In Q3 of this year, I participated in the Shopee Code League, an intense series of 8 challenges conducted over a period of two months. The event was extremely ambitious in its scope and spanned all SEA countries which they were operating in and had high profile guests to kickstart each event, including our very own MOSTI Minister, YB Khairy Jamaluddin.
Shopee-peepeepeepee Most of SEA would be familiar by now with the e-commerce juggernaut that has upended every market in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Delivery Doesn&#39;t Work</title>
      <link>https://aforlorncat1.github.io/blog/food-delivery-doesnt-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 18:55:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aforlorncat1.github.io/blog/food-delivery-doesnt-work/</guid>
      <description>From 2016-2019 I had the privilege of rolling with a start-up through its explosive growth, stagnation, and subsequent demise all in the period of 3 odd years. These are some of the hard-earned lessons gained through my time in the trenches, all of which point to my core thesis that the end-to-end food delivery business model is not viable. This post will be structured as follows:
 Breaking down the lay of the land in 2015 The (apparent) strengths of the business model Why it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work, and the lessons thereof  In the beginning (circa 2015) By now, startup purgatory is filled with the corpses of well-funded attempts such as Munchery, Sprig, Maple, Spoonrocket and our own.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>